luggageonline.com 2005-10-01

# LuggageOnline - Privacy & Security Policy

> Privacy Policy  
> Security Policy

**  
** Luggage Online is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting the personal information you provide online. We've provided this notice to explain how we collect and use and your personal information. If you have any questions regarding this policy, you may direct them to [tjacobsen@luggageonline.com](mailto:tjacobsen@luggageonline.com). 

**What information do we collect? How do we use it?**  
We use your personal information solely to help us service your account, to improve our services to you, to provide you with the products you have requested, and to inform you about additional products or services that may be of interest to you. We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive.

**Will Luggage Online disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**  
Luggage Online will never sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.  
**  
How does Luggage Online use cookies?**  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to provide tailored information from our web site and store items in your shopping cart between visits. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies. However, you can change the settings in your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.

**A special note concerning children’s privacy.**  
The safety of children is obviously very important to us. Children should always ask a parent or guardian for permission before sending personal information to anyone online. Luggage Online does not knowingly collect or maintain information at our website from those who are under 18.

**Is there anything else I should know?**  
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online – on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas – that information can be collected and used by others. In addition, the privacy policies of other websites will vary, while many will have no stated privacy policy. 

In short, if you provide personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. It is ultimately your responsibility to maintain the secrecy of your personal information to the extent you feel comfortable. We encourage you to be careful and to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

**Your Consent**  
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Luggage Online. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

back to top^

**How does Luggage Online protect customer information?**  
When you place an order or access your account information, our servers use Secure Sockets Layers (SSL). SSL encrypts, or scrambles, your information while in transit to us, and it can only be decrypted, or unscrambled, by an authorized computer. Furthermore, all the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
